ZIV MAHLUF

054-6656993

https://www.zivmahluf.com

Ziv5467@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/zivmahluf/ https://github.com/ZivMahluf

Unity Developer focusing on AR & VR development, with vast experience in building projects from scratch, collaborating with design teams and working with customers. My skill set includes designing, implementing and deploying VR application to all types of Oculus headsets (Go, Rift, Quest 1&2). Lecturer for VR Unity development (basic and advanced courses). Researched the field of Redirected Walking (subfield of VR).

Experience

MARCH 2021 – PRESENT FREELANCE UNITY DEVELOPER

- Developing a Snapchat lookalike AR camera app for iOS devices using AR Foundation and OpenCV for Unity.
- Created immersive AR content with Resonai's SDK in Safra Square, Jerusalem. Developed advanced mechanics and tools for optimization. Built for WebGL. https://www.tohucollective.com/postourisma
- Built interaction-focused 2D apps and games for tablets, phones and computers.
- Maintained and extended code in various apps, including 3D Navigation, Maintenance and IOT.

MARCH 2021 – SEPTEMBER 2022 RESEARCH ASSISTANT, LECTURER, THE HEBREW UNIVERSITY OF JERUSALEM

- Researched the field of Redirected Walking (under the guidance of Prof. Yair Bartal), a field that combines my passion for Virtual Reality and Artificial Intelligence.
- Taught students to develop VR applications and games using Unity. The course focuses on building a large VR project in teams of programmers, designers and musicians.

JANUARY 2020 - MARCH 2021 UNITY DEVELOPER, INSOMNIA

- Single handedly carried the development process of various VR and AR applications, from an abstract idea to a working product.
- Designed and built Al-driven applications, using Speech-To-Text and Text-To-Speech engines (GCP, Azure), for both Hebrew and English.
- Extensive knowledge of commonly used libraries, such as AR Foundation, Oculus SDK (including Lip Sync, Avatars, etc.), VRTK and more.
- Deployed for all types of Oculus headsets (Go, Quest 1&2, Rift).

Education

2017-2021 B.SC. COMPUTER SCIENCE, THE HEBREW UNIVERSITY OF JERUSALEM

Majored in Data Science (Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Deep Learning) and Game Development (Computer Graphics, VR Unity Development, Advanced VR Unity Development).

Projects

- Developed a pseudo-psychological-evaluation VR experience. The project was a collaboration between designers from Bezalel and programmers from HUJI.
- Developed an AI agent to play Durak, exceeding 99%-win rate against 3 players.
- Developed a face-mask detector, using real-time video footage taken by a Raspberry Pi camera.

Languages: Hebrew – Native, English – Native level.